<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:padding="20dp"
    android:background="#F2E6C6"
    android:id="@+id/interface2"
    tools:context=".MainActivity">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="vertical">

        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/andlogo"
            android:layout_width="240dp"
            android:layout_height="240dp"
            android:layout_marginTop="20dp"
            android:layout_gravity="center"
            android:src="@drawable/tkklogo"/>

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/title"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="20dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="15dp"
            android:text="Introduction"
            android:textColor="#B16F5B"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            android:textSize="30sp"
            android:shadowColor="@color/white"
            android:shadowRadius="15"
            android:shadowDx="1"
            android:shadowDy="1"/>

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/introduction"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="15dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="15dp"
            android:textColor="@color/black"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            android:textSize="14sp"
            android:shadowColor="@color/white"
            android:shadowRadius="10"
            android:shadowDx="1"
            android:shadowDy="1"
            android:justificationMode="inter_word"
            android:letterSpacing="0.07"
            android:text="Tan Kah Kee Tan Lack Sye Young Inventors' Competition was established in May 1986, advocated by Nobel Laureate Professor Yang Chen Ning, also advisor of Tan Kah Kee Foundation. Professor Yang had recommended this award to encourage students and young people to engage themselves more in invention and creation instead of focusing solely on exam results.\n\nIn 2002, this award was extended to the universities in Shanghai. The participants included students and staff from both universities and high schools in Shanghai.\n\nIn 2010, Nantah Education and Research Foundation reached an agreement with Singapore Tan Kah Kee International Society to jointly organize the Tan Kah Kee Young Tan Lark Sye Young Inventors Competition in Malaysia(TKK). In 2011, New Era College has became a co-organiser. The objectives of Tan Kah Kee Tan Lark Sye Young Inventors’ Competition are to:\n\n•Encourage young people to use their knowledge and skills imaginatively and creatively;\n\n•Stimulate creativity among our youths and promote scientific and technological research in the country;\n\n•Discover new talents;\n\n•Inspire our youths to constantly think of new and creative ways of solving problems;\n\n•Inculcate into our youths an innovative approach in life and in learning.\n\nIn 2011, this award was only opened to the 8 Chinese High Schools in Kuala Lumpur and Selangor. In 2012, this award was further extended to Negeri Sembilan and the National-type secondary schools. Starting from 2015, the competition is open to all the Chinese independent schools in Malaysia as well as all national type secondary school in Selangor, Negeri Sembilan and Melaka.\n\nThe committee members of TKK include the representatives from Singapore Tan Kah Kee International Society, Nantah Foundation and New Era College, Malaysia. The judges include professionals in the fields of Physics, Chemistry, Biology and Engineering.\n"/>

        <Button
            android:id="@+id/btnback"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Back"
            android:textColor="@color/black"
            android:textSize="15sp"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
            android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="10dp"
            android:backgroundTint="#F6B82E"
            android:layout_weight="1"/>

        <Button
            android:id="@+id/btnnext"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Next"
            android:textColor="@color/black"
            android:textSize="15sp"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
            android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="10dp"
            android:layout_weight="1"
            android:backgroundTint="#F6B82E" />

    </LinearLayout>
</ScrollView>